Regine Margallo

+639424578026 · reginem.dev@gmail.com Dasmariñas City, Cavite 4114

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

A recent Information Technology graduate with specialization in web development. A passion for problem-solving drives my ambition to contribute innovative solutions to complex technical challenges. Looking forward to apply my skills in a collaborative environment where I can continue to expand my knowledge and expertise.

EXPERIENCE

Nexxus Lab March 2023 - May 2023

Backend Developer Intern

- Worked on 11 different projects for both mobile and web platforms
- Collaborated with the development team to understand project requirements and translate them into a scalable and efficient system design
- Participated in discussions and contribute ideas for improving system performance, security, and scalability
- Researched and evaluated new technologies, frameworks, and tools for development
- Helped in creating project timelines, milestones, and deliverable schedules

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2019 - 2021

Student Assistant

· Provided general administrative support, such as maintaining filing systems and retrieving data and files

EDUCATION

De La Salle University - Dasmariñas

2019 - 2023

Information Technology with specialization in Web Development

- Department of Science & Technology Undergraduate Scholar, 2019 2023
- Financial Aid Grant Scholar, 2019 2022
- Dean's Honor List, 2019 2023
- TOEIC Certified Professional Proficiency in English
- Developed robust, user-friendly software applications for academic requirements, across mobile, web, and Windows platforms

Congressional Integrated High School

2019 - 2023

Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics Strand

• Developed Windows applications using Visual Basic and SQL

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

- Languages: C; C++; C#.NET; Java; JavaScript; PHP; Python; SQL
- Web: ASP.NET; Bootstrap; Laravel; React
- Mobile: Java; Flutter
- Database: Microsoft SQL Server; MySQL; MongoDB
- Web Design: Adobe Creative Suite; Figma

SOFT SKILLS

- Accountability
- Adaptability
- · Critical thinking Skills
- Communication Skills
- Self-learning
- Time management